# Karolina Ruda

+48 519 184 982 · karolina1998@vip.onet.pl · Szczecin, Poland

 $\frac{https://github.com/KarolinaR98}{https://karolinar98.github.io/my-portfolio/} \cdot \frac{https://karolinar98.github.io/my-portfolio/}{https://karolinar98.github.io/my-portfolio/}$ 

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Skilled IT Engineer with 4 years of experience in the mobile games industry. I am currently focused on developing my skills in front-end development. My passion for technology, strong understanding of the visual aspects of applications, and attention to detail, which I honed as a technical artist, allow me to excel in roles that combine design and programming. I am ready for a new career path where I can blend my creativity with technical expertise to deliver modern and intuitive front-end solutions.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

HTML WordPress Clean Code
CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, RWD MongoDB Strategic thinking
JavaScript, TypeScript C# Problem-solving
ReactJS, Redux GIT Fast learner
jQuery, AJAX Figma, Adobe Photoshop Time managemnet

REST API Visual Studio SCRUM

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Factory 2021 - 2024

#### **Technical Artist**

Worked on the development and optimization of a mobile game with over 10 million users. Paid particular attention to the visual layer and the responsiveness of the application. Recognized for efficiency, reliability, attention to detail, and commitment to improving the project. Successfully streamlined several processes and prepared project documentation.

Game Factory 2020 - 2021

#### **QA Specialist**

Identifying, reporting, and tracking bugs to ensure smooth gameplay.

### Educational Foundation "Równe Szanse"

2020

#### **Unity Developer (Internship)**

Developing and implementing game systems using C#, optimizing performance, debugging, and working on game design and logic. Importing assets and maintaining clear technical documentation.

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **B.S.** in Computer Science

West Pomeranian Business School 2017-2021

Front End Developer Course - Akademia 108

## **CLA - C Programming Language Certified Associate**

#### LANGUAGES

Polish - Native English - C1

#### **INTRESTS**

Music and piano playing Running Psychology